Yeah.
Colin, this was not no particular brand I would call out on stocking.
I think this was across the board.
It was not just in one thing.
It was not just a single geography, but multiple geographies.
And I would not attribute this to a specific drug, the stocking.
Yeah.
And maybe just to provide a little bit of color as well.
I mean, this was related to the implementation of our new SAP system,
where it's often the case when we roll that out in multiple geographies,
we do have to shift stocking levels for the cutover to the new SAP system.
So that's the driver.
And the reason why,
it's not associated with one brand per se.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Michael Leuchten from Jefferies.
Please go ahead.
Thank you for the follow-up.
Vas, interested in your Semblix comment about the second half aiming for NBRX leadership in the US.
Is that just natural progression of the dynamics that we're seeing
or is there a pivot point that would inflect that further?
Yeah.
Thanks, Michael.
I think, I think, yes, it's just the momentum we're seeing.
I also think that,
you know, now we've gotten very strong access position for the brand.
And so I think that stronger access position as it flows through.
I mean, one of the things with CML is because it is a rare disease
and there's a limited number of newly diagnosed patients in a given year.
It just takes time.
And so any of the smaller fluctuations that you see quarter on quarter,
is driven by very few patients.
But all indications we're seeing is that given the very strong safety profile that physicians are seeing with the drug and the known efficacy profile, there's just a lot of momentum now.
So that gives us confidence that we'll get to that market leadership position in the U.S.
And I'll flag again, I mentioned in my opening comments that we're really just at the beginning now of moving from third line to first line ex-U.S.
And I think one of the things that's been a positive trend as well, there are multiple generic medicines available in that first line setting.
There seems to be a strong demand from physicians, but also payers are accepting the fact that Semblitz has demonstrated that it is a superior medicine in that front line setting and more openness to give us the reimbursement we would expect for such a medicine.